A Guide to the Policy Office: General Assembly Legislation of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1990-1993.
Library of Virginia
- General Assembly Legislation, 1990.
  - House of Delegates Bills, 1990.
    - HB 376 (90) Bonds of educational institutions, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - HB 379 (90) Conservators of the peace, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - HB 380 (90) Virginia Residential Landlord and Tenant Act, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - HB 381 (90) Foreclosure notices, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - HB 382 (90) Distribution of drugs, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - HB 383 (90) Perpetual care funds, pre-need burial contracts, and consumer protections, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - HB 384 (90) Consumer finance companies, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - HB 385 (90) Freedom of Information Act, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - HB 386 (90) State Corporation Commission - Insurance policy forms, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - HB 389 (90) Court Appointed Special Advocate Program, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - HB 392 (90) Sale of drugns on or near certain properties, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - HB 395 (90) Life insurance companies - Valuation of reserves, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - HB 396 (90) Title insurance companies - Loss or claim reserves, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - HB 401 (90) Insurance fees, charges and premiums, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - HB 402 (90) Medicare supplement policies, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - HB 404 (90) Alcoholic Beverage Control, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - HB 405 (90) Driver's licences, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - HB 411 (90) School term lengths, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - HB 413 (90) County of Roanoke - Police force, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - HB 414 (90) List of tenants for tax purposes, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - HB 415 (90) Virginia Retail Franchising Act, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - HB 416 (90) Marine Patrols Fund, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - HB 417 (90) Board and Dept. of Rights for the Disabled, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - HB 419 (90) Haul seine nets, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - HB 420 (90) County administrators, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - HB 421 (90) Crab traps and crab pounds, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - HB 423 (90) Highway projects - Use and value engineering, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - HB 426 (90) Sunshading or tinting on windshields and windows, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - HB 431 (90) Child Protective Services investigations, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - HB 432 (90) Bingo receipts and disursements, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - HB 433 (90) Estimated income tax payments, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - HB 436 (90) Baylor Survey, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - HB 437 (90) Certificates of public need, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - HB 443 (90) Abandonment of public roads, landings and crossings, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - HB 444 (90) Local government powers, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - HB 453 (90) Involuntary treatment of mental illness, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - HB 454 (90) Transportation of the mentally ill, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - HB 456 (90) Involuntary treatment of the mentally ill, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - HB 458 (90) Capital cases - Sentencing proceedings, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - HB 459 (90) State grievance procedure, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - HB 460 (90) Rockfish River - Scenic designation, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - HB 462 (90) Corporate stock - Classes and shares, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - HB 463 (90) Hampton Roads Sanitation District Commission, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - HB 464 (90) Local government in land use matters, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - HB 466 (90) Local transportation districts, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - HB 468 (90) Commissioner of Revenue, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - HB 469 (90) Virginia Transportation Council, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - HB 472 (90) Local governments - Voluntary settlements, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - HB 473 (90) Affordable dwelling unit ordinances, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - HB 475 (90) Consolidation agreements, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - HB 476 (90) Storage batteries, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - HB 478 (90) County boards of supervisors, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - HB 482 (90) Compensation for partial incapacity, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - HB 485 (90) Exceptions for the moratorium regarding certificates of public need, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - HB 486 (90) Medical evidence in juvenile and domestic relations district court, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - HB 489 (90) Special county funds for highway purposes, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - HB 490 (90) Consumer utility tax rate on churches in certain localities, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - HB 491 (90) Self proved wills, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - HB 492 (90) Shareholder agreements, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - HB 493 (90) Corporate officers - Resignation and removal, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - HB 494 (90) Foreign corporation mergers, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - HB 496 (90) IRS vouchers for wire transfer, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - HB 497 (90) Beneficiary accounts - Direct payments, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - HB 498 (90) Mutual funds affiliated with a beneficiary, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - HB 499 (90) Commission for the Preservation of the Capitol, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - HB 501 (90) Parking regulations, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - HB 502 (90) Stuart W. Connock, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - HB 504 (90) Manufactured Housing Construction and Safety Standards Law of the Uniform Building Code, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - HB 506 (90) Rule of 78, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - HB 510 (90) State interpreter services for the hearing impaired, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - HB 511 (90) Voter registrars, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - HB 512 (90) Telephone service - Reductions on extensions, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - HB 522 (90) Sheriff's departments, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - HB 532 (90) Retirement benefits, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - HB 534 (90) State Water Commission, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - HB 535 (90) Mammograms, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - HB 538 (90) Endangered species, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - HB 539 (90) Statewide Fire Prevention Code, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - HB 540 (90) Abandoned family graveyards, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - HB 543 (90) Recycling reports, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - HB 545 (90) Jury lists and service, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - HB 549 (90) City charters, annexation notices and county immunity proceedings, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - HB 552 (90) Lawn cutting requirements, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - HB 553 (90) Small claims court, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - HB 554 (90) Small claims court, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - HB 556 (90) Child abuse and neglect, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - HB 559 (90) Shooting or throwing missiles at trains or motor vehicles, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - HB 563 (90) Tanning facilities, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - HB 568 (90) Reckless endangerment by throwing objects from places higher than one story, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - HB 573 (90) Governor as Director of Emergency Services, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - HB 576 (90) Circuit Court order books, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - HB 578 (90) Determination of child or spousal support, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - HB 582 (90) Emancipation of minors, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - HB 585 (90) Restoration of maiden name, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - HB 586 (90) Wet Settlement Act, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - HB 587 (90) Crab pots, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - HB 588 (90) Bingo games and raffles, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - HB 589 (90) Length of fish structures, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - HB 592 (90) Statute of fraud, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - HB 594 (90) Disqualification of trustees, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - HB 595 (90) Long-term care insurance, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - HB 598 (90) Loss ratio standards for long-term care insurance, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - HB 599 (90) Removal, immobilization and storage of certain vehicles - Local control, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - HB 602 (90) Transportation contract revenue bonds, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - HB 603 (90) Criminal history record check for transfer of firearms, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - HB 604 (90) Tennessee Valley Authority payments, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - HB 605 (90) Operation of vehicles by habitual offenders, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - HB 606 (90) Equitable distribution, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - HB 607 (90) Divorce suit record sequestration, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - HB 609 (90) Virginia Coalfield Economic Development Authority, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - HB 611 (90) Coal Surface Mining Reclamation Fund, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - HB 612 (90) Division of Debt Collection with the Dept. of Law, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - HB 613 (90) Sewage definitions, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - HB 614 (90) Motor vehicle sales and use tax, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - HB 618 (90) Reciprocal insurance, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - HB 619 (90) Foreign corporations - Authority to transact business, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - HB 620 (90) Limited partnerships, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - HB 621 (90) Professional corporations, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - HB 622 (90) Trade secrets, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - HB 623 (90) Dulles Access Road, Dulles Toll Road, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - HB 625 (90) Branch pilot licenses, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - HB 626 (90) Liability insurers and rate service organizations, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - HB 627 (90) Liability insurance rates, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - HB 632 (90) Virginia Contractor Transaction Recovery Fund, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - HB 635 (90) Violations of zoning ordinances, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - HB 636 (90) Taxation of daily rental property, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - HB 637 (90) Comprehensive prevention plan, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - HB 639 (90) Subdivision ordinances, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - HB 640 (90) Asbestos regulations, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - HB 641 (90) Campaign contribution and expenditures, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - HB 642 (90) School board access to employee criminal records, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - HB 644 (90) State Police Officers' Retirement System, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - HB 645 (90) Board for Architects, Engineers, Land Surveyors and Landscape Architects, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - HB 647 (90) Exclusion of witnesses in a criminal trial, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - HB 650 (90) Procedure on forfeited bonds, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - HB 653 (90) Posted service and mailing requirements, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - HB 654 (90) Licensure by endorsement, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - HB 656 (90) Wild birds and wild animals - hunting, trapping, selling and transporting, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - HB 659 (90) Fire bombs, explosive devices and hoax explosive devices, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - HB 660 (90) Possession of firearms and controlled substances, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - HB 661 (90) Reports to attorney for the Commonwealth of unexecuted criminal process, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - HB 665 (90) Disorderly conduct, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - HB 666 (90) Athletic Boarcd, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - HB 667 (90) Road tax on motor fuel, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - HB 668 (90) Urban Development Corporation Act, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - HB 670 (90) Governor's Council on Alcohol and Drug Abuse Problems, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - HB 673 (90) Local telephone charges, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - HB 674 (90) Real Estate Appraisal Board, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - HB 675 (90) Marion Little League Baseball, Inc., 1990. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - HB 676 (90) Virginia Spill Response Team, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - HB 679 (90) Pharmacists - Licensure by endorsement, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - HB 680 (90) Summary judgment, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - HB 681 (90) Board of Pharmacy, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - HB 682 (90) Virginia Racing Commission, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - HB 683 (90) Dept. of Air Pollution Control, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - HB 684 (90) Low income housing credit and Virginia tax credit, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - HB 685 (90) Transportation of juveniles, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - HB 686 (90) Public service corps, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - HB 689 (90) Recordation tax - exemptions, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - HB 690 (90) Freedom of Information Act, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - HB 692 (90) R.E. Lee Camp Confederate Memorial Park, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - HB 694 (90) Incarceration in state and local correctional facilities, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - HB 700 (90) Virginia Organic Food Act, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - HB 702 (90) Towing and immobilization of vehicles, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - HB 703 (90) Valuation of real estate, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - HB 705 (90) Industrial Development Authority, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - HB 707 (90) Solid waste management plans, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - HB 715 (90) Unclaimed property notices, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - HB 717 (90) Gas severance tax, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - HB 720 (90) Condemnation proceedings, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - HB 721 (90) Zoning ordinances, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - HB 725 (90) Jerry Lynn Hines and Carol Black Hines, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - HB 728 (90) Juvenile and Domestice Relations District Courts, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - HB 730 (90) Tax refunds for building materials, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - HB 731 (90) Comprehensive plans, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - HB 736 (90) Refunds for excessive insurance premiums, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - HB 738 (90) Dept. and State Board of Youth Services, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - HB 739 (90) Racing horses under false names, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - HB 740 (90) Virginia Racing Commission, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - HB 743 (90) Ineffective assistance of counsel, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - HB 744 (90) Improper driving, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - HB 745 (90) Commercial driver's licenses, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - HB 746 (90) Overweight limits for concrete haulers, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - HB 747 (90) Reforestation Board, State Forester, and Dept. of Forestry, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - HB 748 (90) Motor vehicle dealers, dealer-operators and sales persons, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - HB 753 (90) Local regulation of alcoholic beverages, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - HB 754 (90) Alcoholic beverage sales, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - HB 755 (90) Sewage disposal and alternative discharging sewage systems, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - HB 760 (90) Prosecution for tax offenses, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - HB 761 (90) Venue for prosecution of tax crimes, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - HB 762 (90) Council of Information Management, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - HB 765 (90) Public hearings on issuance of bonds, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - HB 766 (90) Middle Atlantic Interstate Forest Fire Protection Compact, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - HB 769 (90) Special service districts, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - HB 770 (90) Motor Vehicle Warranty Enforcement Act, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - HB 771 (90) Government Non-Arbitrage Investment Act, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - HB 772 (90) Involuntary detention of the mentally ill, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - HB 775 (90) Financing housing developments, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - HB 776 (90) Reporting offenses to school authorities, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - HB 777 (90) Standards of quality, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - HB 779 (90) Unfunded scholarships, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - HB 780 (90) Sales of alcoholic beverages, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - HB 781 (90) Compulsorty training for private security services, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - HB 789 (90) Abandonment of roads, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - HB 770 (90) Smoke detectors, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - HB 791 (90) State Registrar of Vital Records, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - HB 793 (90) Comprehensive zoning ordinances, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - HB 795 (90) Parole, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - HB 796 (90) Improper disposal of solid waste, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - HB 798 (90) Virginia Racing Commission, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - HB 799 (90) Warrants for arrest, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - HB 800 (90) Detention for psychiatric treatment or evaluation, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - HB 801 (90) Filing pleadings, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - HB 804 (90) Commitment and competency of prisoners, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - HB 805 (90) Transcripts as evidence, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - HB 806 (90) Originals as evidence, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - HB 807 (90) Juvenile court orders, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - HB 808 (90) Elimination of dower, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - HB 809 (90) Brandishing a firearm, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - HB 812 (90) Juvenile courts, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - HB 814 (90) Reporting of disease, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - HB 817 (90) Juvenile and Circuit Courts - Concurrent jurisdiction, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - HB 820 (90) Board and Dept. of Criminal Justice Services, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - HB 821 (90) Pension and retirement laws, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - HB 824 (90) Circuit Court Clerks, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - HB 827 (90) Virginia Public Records Act, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - HB 828 (90) Filing financing statements, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - HB 831 831 (90) Motor vehicle registration fees, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - HB 832 (90) County boards of supervisors, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - HB 833 (90) Speed limits, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - HB 834 (90) Rappahannock River - Natural oyster rock beds and shoals / Baylor survey, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - HB 836 (90) State Police, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - HB 839 (90) Migrant labor camps, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - HB 840 (90) Louis P. Bailey Memorial Highway, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - HB 841(90) James D. Hagood Memorial Highway, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - HB 844 (90) Birth-Related Neurological Injury Compensation Act, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - HB 846 (90) Health histories and immunizations, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - HB 849 (90) State Board of Elections - Primary elections, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - HB 850 (90) Emergency absentee ballots, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - HB 851 (90) Defense of local election officials, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - HB 854 (90) Labeling of plastic container products, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - HB 855 (90) Rcycling, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - HB 856 (90) Disposal of lead acid batteries, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - HB 860 (90) Noise ordinances - Sport shooting ranges, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - HB 862 (90) Commission on Population Growth and Management, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - HB 863 (90) Licensed insurance agents and consultants, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - HB 864 (90) Mixed radioactive waste, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - HB 866 (90) Powers of fiduciaries, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - HB 869 (90) Articles of incorporation, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - HB 870 (90) Control share acquisitions, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - HB 871 (90) Refunds - Small water or sewer utility charges, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - HB 875 (90) Pawnbrokers and precious metal dealers, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - HB 881 (90) Coin operated telephones, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - HB 882 (90) Virginia Public Procurement Act, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - HB 884 (90) Homeowner's insurance, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - HB 888 (90) Subdivision ordinances, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - HB 890 (90) Warrantless arrests, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - HB 892 (90) Teaching scholarship loans, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - HB 893 (90) Tuition assistance, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - HB 894 (90) Motor vehicle manufacturers and distributers - Disclosures, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - HB 900 (90) Real estate tax deferrals, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - HB 902 (90) Plats and site plans for proposed subdivision, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - HB 903 (90) Subdivision ordinance, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - HB 904 (90) Public Telecommunications Fund, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - HB 906 (90) Virginia Marine Patrol, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - HB 916 (90) Corporate income tax, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - HB 917 (90) Rate increases for public utilities, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - HB 923 (90) Punishments for felonies and misdemeanors, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - HB 928 (90) Deaf and hard of hearing - Dual party relay service, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - HB 929 (90) Advisory Committee on Child Abuse and Neglect, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - HB 930 (90) Modifications to home of an injured employee, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - HB 932 (90) Attorney General - Civil matters, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - HB 933 (90) Community Diversion Incentive Act, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - HB 937 (90) Affordable dwelling unit ordinances, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - HB 938 (90) Real property tax increases, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - HB 939 (90) Migratory gases, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - HB 941 (90) Missing children - Records, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - HB 942 (90) Missing children - Reports, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - HB 946 (90) Kindergarten programs, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - HB 947 (90) Financial records - Retention and disposition, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - HB 952 (90) Disciplinary authority of school boards, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - HB 960 (90) Concealed weapons, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - HB 961 (90) Child support enforcement, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - HB 962 (90) Hand gun purchase by law enforcement officers, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - HB 963 (90) Free tuition, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - HB 965 (90) Health spas, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - HB 968 (90) Medical assistance services, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - HB 973 (90) Authority to prohibit leaves and grass clippings, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - HB 974 (90) Solid waste regulations, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - HB 975 (90) Redistricting, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - HB 976 (90) Fish - Russell County, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - HB 978 (90) School boards, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - HB 980 (90) Sewerage system construction, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - HB 982 (90) Removal, immobilization and storage of vehicles, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - HB 985 (90) Free tuition, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - HB 988 (90) Authority to require removal of trash, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - HB 989 (90) Commercial driver training schools, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - HB 990 (90) Replacement of trees, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - HB 992 (90) Tax increment financing, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - HB 993 (90) Motor vehicle emissions inspections, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - HB 994 (90) Perpetual care funds and preneed burial contracts, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - HB 995 (90) Practicl funeral service - Licensure, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - HB 999 (90) Virginia Freedom of Information Act - Closed meetings, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - HB 1002 (90) Virginia Underground Petroleum Storage Tank Fund, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - HB 1006 (90) School dropout prevention, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - HB 1009 (90) Saltwater Sport Fishing Tournament, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - HB 1012 (90) Involuntary detention and admission for treatment of mental illness, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - HB 1013 (90) Commitment or certification order appeals, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - HB 1021 (90) Dog license tax, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - HB 1022 (90) Bright flue-cured tobacco excise tax, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - HB 1024 (90) Transient occupancy tax, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 6)